Hello friends, welcome
to our YouTube channel.  Today we are going to talk
about ICICI's Elevate Plan.  And
today we will know about it in brief
and review it to see for which people this
plan will be best.  And
what are the complications involved in taking this plan?
And in this plan, you will get many
riders etc. in it.  So
you will have to read it in detail first.
Accordingly, we can customize it according to your needs.
So we will
claim it through health insurance.
Its hook is
unlimited, its main benefit is that we
get unlimited health insurance in it, is
this real and just marketing hype, what is the
unlimited health insurance that we get in it, is it just
a
marketing stunt, we will know that too
in detail about this plan, so stay tuned
till the end of the video, what is
Elevate Plan, Elevate Plan
is a kind of customized health insurance plan, in this
you can add riders in it according to your need, you
can add on it, whatever you need, you
will add that rider in it.
You pay its premium.  Inside this you
get individual family floater.
You will have to take a minimum of Rs 5 lakh.  Its cover ranges from Rs 5 lakh to
unlimited.
You can take it as high as you want.  Let me talk about its top
features.
Infinite care comes one.  You
can make unlimited claims under this policy.
You can make claims under this scheme as many times as you want.  Let
me talk about the top features inside it.  The
first is Infinite Care Unlimited
Claim, the second is Unlimited Restoration, the
third is Power Booster, the fourth is Jump Start Add-
on, the first feature is Unlimited Claim,
under this, if you face any emergency during the entire policy term due to which
your claim becomes very high, then
you can take that claim under this.
Suppose you have taken a policy of Rs 10 lakh
and if your claim is of Rs 50 lakh, Rs 60 lakh or Rs
1 crore, then
you can use it once. There is
such a feature in this policy
and the second feature is unlimited
restoration. Suppose you have
taken a family floater and you have faced an
emergency and your Rs 10 lakh has been exhausted
or out of that Rs 10 lakh, you have
used Rs 6-7 lakh and if you
need it again, then it will be restored and it becomes a
policy of Rs 10 lakh again.
If you take a claim for it again, then
you will keep getting this unlimited restoration in it.
Meaning, in a way
you will take out water from the jug and then the
jug will get filled again automatically.  So in this
way this restoration is unlimited
inside it.  Power Booster is a feature that
can increase your sum insured unlimited times.  Suppose you have taken a policy of Rs 10 lakh.
What happens in the rest of the company
?  It increases by 20% in the claim free year and at the end it is
50% and goes up to 100%.
But what will happen by installing a power booster?  Suppose
you have taken a policy of Rs 10 lakh.  She will be worth Rs
20 lakh to you next year.  In this way,
it will keep increasing by Rs 30 lakh and will reach unlimited.
But this is an add on.  All these are
extra charges.  If you do
not take this add-on, then it increases according to the normal policy by 20%.
What is Jump Star Add On Inside?  Suppose you have a pre-
existing disease, then
you have to wait for 2 years
or 3 years for that pre-existing disease.
You want to eliminate it by paying extra
so that your existing disease gets
covered from day one.  So jump
start you can add that.
You can avail Infinite Care One Time Unlimited Claim Benefit
under this.  As I
told you, beyond sum insured,
you can claim infinitely beyond your sum insured.
You can take one time unlimited claim in this.
Unlimited Restoration: I have already discussed and
told you about it.  Sum insured refills
happen.  You can do it multiple times.
Even after multiple claims if
you are getting repeated claims.  Regarding the same problem, it
gives some such problems.   If
claims are coming again and again, it will keep getting
restored again and again.  This feature
is inside it.  Power Booster 100% Bonus will increase
yearly.  Even after claim, whether you have
taken a claim or not,
your power booster benefit is that it will
increase 100% year on year.  And it goes
unlimited.  Jump Start: I have
told you that pre-adjusting diseases will be
covered after 30 days.
End core coverage: Under this, hospitalization,
your pre-hospitalization expenses, everything is
covered.  Ayush is also covered under it.
Ambulance, organ donor, everything is covered
under it.  All other features are available in this model with
no room capping.  Everything is covered in it.   The
whole of India is cashless.  Worldwide
emergency is also covered under it.  There
is also an air ambulance.  There is tele consultation.  All the
features are inside it.  And there are also special benefits in it.
You can also take maternity cover.
New born baby cover can be taken.
If you want to take chronic disease management
separately, then you
can take that also as an add-on.  Maternity
cover is also available as an add-on.  It is not inbuilt in it.
If you need it, you
can add it to the policy.
This is a fully customized plan.
You can add on whatever you need.
We add add ons to most of the
clients.  Just like there is a
claim protector, there is an inflation
protector.  You can add room rent modifier,
worldwide cover etc.
You can take any room within the room rent modifier.
You can also take inflation protector inside it.  It is according to your need.
If you want worldwide coverage also,
you can add that cover also inside it.
What is the prose of this?
What is this plan?  Let me tell you briefly.
Highly customizable.  I have already told you.
Whatever features you want, if you feel
that you need this thing in your health insurance, then
you can add it in it.  It has
advanced features inside it.
Every type of advanced feature will be available in this policy.
You will not have any such feature.  There
are many advanced features in your basic policies.  You will get all
types of covers.
You can add on whatever you want in it.  This is a
long term cover, you have
unlimited sum insured under it.  You
can claim as much as you want.   It is
expensive as an add-on.
This is also one of its members.  Yes sir.  For example, if you add a
lot of add-ons, its premium will
increase accordingly.  So
its structure is quite complex also.  Many
people will not understand this plan.   There are
so many add ons.  Which one should I take and
which one should I not take?  So whenever you plan to take this
plan, then
you must take health insurance under someone's guidance.
If you find it right online, you can take it.
But you should prefer to
take it through an offline intermediate, as
more things become clear to you and later in the
future you will also get help at the time of claim.
Those things are
not possible online.  Should you buy?  Whether you
should buy this or not
depends on your family,
what kind of family you have?
How are your long term plans?  If you want high cover
then this plan is the best because
till now there is no plan in high cover which
gives you infinite cover.  There are still some companies
but their premiums are also very high.  There
is also a Tata plan.  I will
bring a comparison for that too.  But it is
not even unlimited inside it.  The sum
insured also increases in that.  But if ICICI has a good
brand value then it will be better.  Should
you avoid?  If your budget is low
and you want a simple plan then this
plan is not for you because it has a
lot of customization.  If you go and purchase it normally,
you will not get anything in it.  All the things in it will have to be
taken by adding on.  That is why I have
told you that
if you want to join us with the help of a professional, then
I can help you completely in
this plan.  You contact me.
I will give you my
WhatsApp number also.  You contact there.
I will
send you the proper plan quotation etc. as per your need along with
riders.  You can decide whether
you want to take it or not.  The rest is your
decision.  And if you
face any problem, or want more
details about the plan, you
can comment to me on Elevate.  The name of its plan
is Elevate.  And you can subscribe
to the channel, more videos are coming.
Insurance related also through mutual funds.
So you should subscribe
to that channel and you will get good ideas.  Ok
friends have a nice day.  Bye Bye